BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11) 6178/011
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11)
1959- 1967
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States. Department of Labor
Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS)
6178/011
7 cubic feet
7 linear ft.
Collective labor agreements.
Union wage agreements obtained in the July 1, 1962 surveys in the building trades, printing trades, local trucking, and local transit industries.
5833610
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 11, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 21, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178/001: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1) 6178/002: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/004: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/006: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6) 6178/007: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7) 6178/008: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/009: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/010: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/012: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/013: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/014: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/015: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/016: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16) 6178/017: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/018: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/019: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/020: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/021(d): BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 21) Digital 6178/022 mf: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm 6178/023: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23)
Collective labor agreements -- United States; United States. Department of Labor. Bureau of Labor Statistics
5833610
- Asbestos Workers; Boilermakers; Bricklayers; Carpenters; Cement Finishers; Elevators Contractors; Electricians; Engineers; Glaziers. 1948-1964. (Box 1)
  - Asbestos Workers, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    14 Workers Agreement Booklets
  - Asbestos Workers, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Boiler makers, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    26 Workers Agreement Booklets
  - Brick Layers, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bricklayers, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Carpenters, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    5 Agreement Booklets
  - Carpenters, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    7 Agreement Booklets
  - Carpenters, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Cement Finishers, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Elevator Contractors, 1962-1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    30 Agreement Booklets
  - Elevator Contractors, 1962-1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Electricians, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    9 Agreement Booklets
  - Electricians, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Engineers, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Engineers, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    12 Agreement Booklets
  - Engineers, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Glaziers, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Lathers; Machinists; Marble Setters; Mosaic and Terrazzo Workers; Painters; Pipefitters; Plasterers; Plumbers; Building Trades; Roofers; Sheet-Metal Workers. 1959-1964. (Box 2)
  - Lathers, 1961-1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Machinists, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Marble Setters, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Mosaic and Terrazzo Workers, 1959-1962 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Painters, 1959-1962 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    4 Agreement Booklets
  - Painters, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Pipe Fitters, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Pipe Fitters, 1947-1962 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    8 Agreement Booklets
  - Plasterers, 1959-1962 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Plasterers, 1957-1962 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Plumbers, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Plumbers, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Building Trades, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Wage Booklet
  - Building Trades, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Building Trades, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Roofers, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Sheet-Metal Workers, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Sheet-Metal Workers, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    6 Agreement Booklets
- Structural-Iron Workers; Stonemasons; Tile Layers; Laborers; Marble Setters' Helpers; Plumbers' Laborers; Plasterers' Laborers; Terrazzo Workers' Helpers; Tile Layers' Helpers; Atlanta-- Transit; Baltimore-- Transit; Birmingham-- Transit; Boston-- Transit (Box 3)
  - Structural-Iron Workers, 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Stone Masons, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Tile Layers, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Laborers, 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    11 Agreement Booklets
  - Laborers, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    10 Agreement Booklets
  - Marble Setters' Helpers, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Plumbers' Laborers, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    1 Agreement Booklet
  - Plasterers laborers, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Terrazzo Workers' Helpers, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Tile Layers' Helpers, 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Atlanta-Transit, 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    1 Agreement Booklet; June 21 1960 - June 20 1963
  - Baltimore-Transit, 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    1 Agreement Booklet; October 1 1960 - September 30 1962
  - Birmingham-Transit, 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    1 Agreement Booklet; April 1 1960 - March 31 1963
  - Boston-Transit, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Buffalo-Transit, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    1 Agreement Booklet; August 1 1960
  - Charlotte-Transit, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    October 16 1960
  - Chicago-Transit, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    December 1 1959
  - Cincinnati-Transit, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Cleveland-Transit, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    July 1 1961
  - Columbus-Transit, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    1 Agreement Booklet; October 15 1961 - September 28 1963
  - Denver-transit, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    May 1 1962
  - Erie-Transit, 1959-1961 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    October 2 1959 - October 1 1961
  - Houston-Transit, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    7-1-1962
  - Little Rock-Transit, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    June 1 1961
  - Louisville-Transit, 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    1; January 1 1960 - December 31 1962
  - Los Angeles-Transit, 1961-1964 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Milwaukee-Transit, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Minneapolis-St. Paul-Transit, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    1 Agreement Booklet; March 1 1961 - February 28 1963
  - Newark-Transit, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    1 Agreement Booklet; February 1 1962
  - New haven-Transit, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    1 Agreement Booklet; July 1 1961 - September 30 1963
  - New Orleans-Transit (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - New York-Transit, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Pittsburgh-Transit, 1961-1964 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Richmond-Transit, 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    2 Agreement Booklets
  - Salt Lake City-Transit, 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    1 Agreement Booklet; September 1 1960 - August 31 1962
  - San Antonio-Transit, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - San Diego-Transit, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    1 Agreement Booklet; June 1 1961 - June 1 1963
  - San Francisco-Oakland-Transit, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    1 Agreement Booklet; October 28 1960
  - Seattle-Transit, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    1 Agreement Booklet; November 1 1961 - October 31 1963
  - Spokane-Transit, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    January 1 1961 - December 31 1962
  - Springfield-Transit, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    October 1 1961 - September 30 1962
  - Syracuse-Transit, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    1 Agreement Booklet; November 1 1961
  - Bookbinders, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Bookbinders (B and J), 1959-1964 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    21 Agreement Booklets
  - Compositors (B and J), 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    13 Agreement Booklets
  - Compositors (B and J), 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Stereotypers and Electrotypers (B&J); Mailers (B&J); Photoengravers (B&J); Pressmen (B&J); Compositors, Newspaper; Mailers, Newspaper; Photoengravers, Newspaper; Pressmen, Newspaper. 1954- 1964. (Box 4)
  - Stereotypers and Electrotypers (B and J), 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stereotypers and Electrotypers (B and J), 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stereotypers and Electrotypers (B and J), 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Mailers-Book and Job, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Photoengravers (B and J), 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Photoengraves (B and J), 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Photoengravers (B and J), 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Pressmen (B and J), 1959-1963 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Pressmen (B and J), 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Pressmen (B and J), 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Compositors, Newspaper, 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    24 Agreement Booklets
  - Mailers, Newspaper, 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Mailers, Newspaper, 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Photoengravers, Newspaper, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Photoengravers, Newspaper, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Pressmen, Newspaper, 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Pressmen, Newspaper, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Stereotypers, Newspaper; Atlanta-- Local Trucking; Baltimore-- Local Trucking; Birmingham-- Local Trucking; Boston-- Local Transit; Buffalo-- Local Transit; Chicago-- Local Trucking; Cincinnati-- Local Trucking; Cleveland-- Local Trucking; Columbus-- Loca (Box 5)
  - Stereotypers, Newspaper, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Atlanta-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Baltimore-Local trucking, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Birmingham-Local Trucking, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Buffalo-Local Trucking, 1961-1967 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Buffalo-Local Trucking, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Chicago-Local Trucking, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Cleveland-Local Trucking, 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Columbus-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Dallas-Local Trucking, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Dayton-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Denver-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Detroit-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Houston-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Grand Rapids-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Indianapolis-Local Trucking, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Jacksonville-Local Trucking, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Kansas City-Local Trucking, 1960-1962 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Knoxville-- Local Trucking; Little Rock-- Local Trucking; Los Angeles-- Local Trucking; Louisville-- Local Trucking; Memphis-- Local Trucking; Milwaukee-- Local Trucking; Minneapolis-St. Paul-- Local Trucking; New Haven-- Local Trucking; New Orleans-- Loc (Box 6)
  - Knoxville-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Little Rock-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Louisville-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Memphis-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Milwaukee-Local Trucking, 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Minneapolis-St. Paul-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Minneapolis-St. Paul-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Minneapolis-St. Paul-Local Trucking, 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - New Haven-Local Trucking, 1960-1967 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - New Orleans-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - New York-Local Trucking, 1962-1964 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Omaha-Local Trucking, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Oklahoma City-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Peoria-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Pittsburgh-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Portland-Local Trucking, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Providence-Local Trucking, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Richmond-Local Trucking, 1959-1961 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Salt lake City-Local Trucking, 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - San Antonio-Local Trucking, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - San Diego-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- San Francisco/Oakland-- Local Trucking; Seattle-- Local Trucking; Spokane-- Local Trucking; Springfield-- Local Trucking; St. Louis- Local Trucking; Toledo-- Local Trucking. 1959-1954. (Box 7)
  - San Francisco/San-Local Trucking, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - San Francisco/Oakland-Local Trucking, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    28 Agreement booklets
  - San Francisco/Oakland-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Seattle-Local Trucking, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Spokane-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Springfield-Local Trucking, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - St. Louis-Local Trucking, 1961-1964 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - St. Louis-Local Trucking, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - St. Louis-Local Trucking, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 9)